90 ROARING MINUTES OF LAUGHS!
Topper is a comedy, fantasy, romance film directed by Norman Z. McLeod.
Madcap couple George and Marion Kerby are killed in an automobile accident.
They return as ghosts to try and liven up the regimented lifestyle
of their friend and bank president, Cosmo Topper.
When Topper starts to live it up, it strains relations with his stuffy wife.
Marion Kerby, played by Constance Bennett.
George Kerby, played by Cary Grant.
Cosmo Topper, played by Roland Young.
Mrs. Topper, played by Billie Burke.
Wilkins, played by Alan Mowbray.
Casey, played by Eugene Pallette.
Topper  is a 1937 American supernatural comedy film starring Constance Bennett and Cary Grant, and
featuring Roland Young, Billie Burke, Alan Mowbray, and Eugene Pallette in support.
Directed by Norman Z.
McLeod, it tells the story of a stuffy, stuck-in-his-ways man who is
haunted by the ghosts of a fun-loving married couple.
The film was adapted by Eric Hatch, Jack Jevne and Eddie
Moran from the 1926 novel by Thorne Smith.
It was produced by Hal Roach and distributed by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer.
Topper was a huge hit with film audiences in the summer of 1937.
Topper was the first black-and-white film to be digitally
colorized, re-released in 1985 by Hal Roach Studios.
The film explores themes of banker, based on novel
or book, bank, car accident, anger.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.